(Leonard:)On account of how sad I am
about my mom.
(Howard:)Leonard, you ready for lunch?
One sec!
(Leonard:)Hey. Sorry.
(Howard:)-Hi, Penny.
-Hi.
(Penny:)All right, sweetie.
You hang in there today.
(Leonard:)I'll try, but I might be sad
again tonight.
(Penny:)Okay.
Wow! Sex at work?!
(Leonard:)Leave it alone.
That's my girlfriend.
(Penny:)-Sorry.
-Who just had sex with me at work!
(Howard:)Damn.
How'd you swing that?
(Leonard:)Whenever I talk about
how awful my mom was,
(Leonard:)Penny will do anything
to make me feel better.
(Howard:)-Seriously?
-Look, I mean...
(Leonard:)I'm not proud of it,
but it does work.
(Leonard:)I got her to watch a six-part
documentary on Monty Python.
(Leonard:)Even I was bored, I just wanted
to see if she'd make it to the end.
(Howard:)You sound kind of proud of it.